<resources>
    <!--    labels resource-->
    <string name="app_name">exer2_madi_b9l</string>
    <string name="start">START</string>
    <string name="retry">RETRY</string>
    <string name="app_header"><b><i>Which Spongebob Squarepants character are you?</i></b></string>
    <string name="scroll_view">Find out which Spongebob Squarepant character are you!</string>
    <string name="start_header"><i>You are:</i></string>

    <!--    character names resource-->
    <string name="spongebob_characters">Spongebob characters</string>
    <string name="gary">Gary</string>
    <string name="larry_the_lobster">Larry</string>
    <string name="spongebob">Spongebob</string>
    <string name="cinderella_name">Cinderella</string>
    <string name="mr_crab">Mr. Crab</string>
    <string name="mrs_puff">Mrs. Puff</string>
    <string name="patrick">Patrick</string>
    <string name="pearl">Pearl</string>
    <string name="plankton">Plankton</string>
    <string name="sandy">Sandy</string>
    <string name="squidward">Squidward</string>


    <!--    descriptions resource (per character)-->
    <!--    descriptions were taken from "https://disney.fandom.com/wiki/The_Disney_Wiki"-->

    <string name="gary_des">
        Gary the Snail (voiced by Tom Kenny) is SpongeBobs pet sea snail who lives with him in
        their pineapple home and vocalizes like a cat. Despite only communicating through meows,
        other characters can understand and talk to him. Depicted as a level-headed character,
        Gary often serves as a voice of reason for SpongeBob and solves problems that his owner
        cannot. He has a pink shell that is impractically spacious on the inside.
    </string>

    <string name="larry_des">
        Larry the Lobster (usually voiced by Mr. Lawrence and voiced by Bill Fagerbakke for a line
        in "MuscleBob BuffPants") is a lobster bodybuilder and workout fanatic who lifts weights.
        He is usually seen at Goo Lagoon alongside Scooter. He first appears in "Ripped Pants".
    </string>

    <string name="spongebob_des">
        SpongeBob SquarePants (voiced by Tom Kenny) is a yellow anthropomorphic sea sponge who
        usually wears brown short pants, a white collared shirt, and a red tie. He lives in a
        pineapple house and is employed as a fry cook at a fast food restaurant called the
        Krusty Krab. He diligently attends Mrs. Puff\'s Boating School but has never passed;
        his lack of a driver\'s license is a running gag throughout the series. He is relentlessly
        optimistic and enthusiastic toward his job and his friends. SpongeBob\'s hobbies include
        catching jellyfish, blowing bubbles, playing with his best friend Patrick, and
        unintentionally irritating his neighbor Squidward. He first appears in "Help Wanted".
    </string>

    <string name="mr_crab_des">
        Eugene Krabs (voiced by Clancy Brown) is a red crab who owns and operates the Krusty Krab
        restaurant where SpongeBob works. He is self-content, cunning, and obsessed with the value
        and essence of money. He lives in an anchor with his teenage daughter Pearl, who is a
        whale. He dislikes spending money but will go to great lengths to make Pearl happy.
        He tends to worry more about his riches than about the needs of his employees.
        Having served in the navy, he loves sailing, whales, sea shanties, and talking
        like a pirate.
    </string>

    <string name="mrs_puff_des">
        Mrs. Puff is SpongeBob/s paranoid driving teacher and the owner of the town boating school,
        which is similar to a driver\'s education facility. She would like nothing more than to pass
        SpongeBob, as he is her most dedicated and hard-working student, but he routinely panics
        when he tries to drive a boat and fails every driving test he takes. His failures often
        result in crashes that lead to mass destruction and endanger Mrs. Puff. While she tries her
        best to be friendly and patient with her students, Mrs. Puff finds SpongeBob\'s
        unintentional recklessness exasperating. She is the long-standing love interest
        and girlfriend of Mr. Krabs.
    </string>

    <string name="patrick_des">
        Patrick Star (voiced by Bill Fagerbakke) is a pink starfish who lives under a rock and
        wears flowered swim trunks. His most prominent character trait is his extremely low
        intelligence. He is best friends with SpongeBob and often unknowingly encourages activities
        that get the two into trouble. While typically unemployed throughout the series,
        Patrick holds various short-term jobs as the storyline of each episode requires.
        He is generally slow and easy-going but can sometimes get aggressive,
        much like real starfish.
    </string>

    <string name="pearl_des">
        Pearl Krabs (voiced by Lori Alan) is a teenage sperm whale and Mr. Krabs daughter.
        She wants to fit in with her fish peers, but finds this impossible to do because of the
        large size inherent to her species. She will inherit the Krusty Krab from her father when
        she grows older, but is still in high school and does not yet have a job at the family
        business. Pearl\'s favorite activities are working at the Bikini Bottom Mall,
        using her father\'s credit card to buy anything that is in style, and listening to pop music.
    </string>

    <string name="plankton_des">
         Sheldon Plankton (voiced by Mr. Lawrence) and Karen Plankton (voiced by Jill Talley)
        are the owners of the Chum Bucket, an unsuccessful restaurant located across the street
        from the Krusty Krab. Their business is a commercial failure because they sell mostly
        inedible foods made from chum. Plankton is a small planktonic copepod and the
        self-proclaimed archenemy of Mr. Krabs. He is a skilled inventor and possesses a Napoleon
        complex due to his short stature. Karen is Plankton\'s own invention, a waterproof
        supercomputer who supplies him with evil plans to steal Krabs\' secret recipe for Krabby
        Patties. She is married to Plankton and usually takes residence in the
        Chum Bucket laboratory.
    </string>

    <string name="sandy_des">
        Sandy Cheeks (voiced by Carolyn Lawrence) is a squirrel from Texas who lives in an
        air-filled glass dome and wears a diving suit to breathe underwater. Whenever any aquatic
        creatures enter her home, they must wear helmets of water. Sandy works as a scientist,
        explorer, and inventor. She is a rodeo champion with a number of athletic interests,
        such as "sand-boarding" and karate. She speaks with a Southern drawl and uses typical
        Southern slang words and phrases.
    </string>

    <string name="squidward_des">
       Squidward Tentacles (voiced by Rodger Bumpass) is an octopus with a large nose who works as
        a cashier at the Krusty Krab. He is SpongeBob\'s next-door neighbor with a dry, sarcastic
        sense of humor. He believes himself to be a talented artist and musician, but nobody
        else recognizes his abilities. He plays the clarinet and often paints self-portraits in
        different styles, which he hangs up around his moai house. Squidward frequently voices his
        frustration with SpongeBob, but he genuinely cares for him deep down. This has been
        revealed in the form of sudden confessions when Squidward is in a dire situation.
    </string>


</resources>
